A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers, Inc. (RBI) (and successors) records FA480
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Investments, A-Z, Accession 1, 1946-1969; 1936-1984; 1; 97.21 Cubic Feet 251 letter document boxes and 4 legal document boxes; Standard storage boxes, Boxes 1-94.
  - Thiokol Chemical - Dyna Star Reports, 1967 (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - Thiokol Chemical - Executive Meetings, 1964-1965 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - Thiokol Chemical - Mergers - General, 1961-1964 (Box 206, Folder 2-3)
  - Thiokol Chemical - McKinsey and Co. Study, 1958 (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - Thiokol Chemical - Mergers - Reaction Motors, 1957-1959 (Box 207, Folder 1)
  - Thiokol Chemical - Treasurer's Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 207, Folder 2)
  - Thompson Trailer Corp., 1949-1957 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    Manufacture light-weight transportation equipment, trailer and special purpose truck bodies. Stock interests of WR, LSR sold. LSR, WR, RHM, AWE, RBM.
  - Thompson Industries, 1946-1962 (Box 207, Folder 4)
    Design and manufacture special machine tool accessories, production of linear action ball bushings. LSR guaranteed Chase loan. No investment. LSR, RBM.
  - Transoceanic Development Corp., 1955-1957 (Box 207, Folder 5)
    Investments to be made in British Commonwealth and other parts of non-communist world. Investments made. RHM, DR, LSR, NAR, ARM.
  - Turbo-Jet Principle, 1951 (Box 207, Folder 6)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Proposed Corporation, 1961-1968 (Box 207, Folder 7)
    Development of nuclear fuel and research in related areas.
  - United Nuclear Corporation - By-Laws, 1961-1968 (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Contract Status, 1961-1968 (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Compensation Committee, 1961-1968 (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Directors Meetings, 1961-1968 (Box 208, Folder 4-6, Box 209, Folder 1)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Eastview Liquidating Corp., 1962 (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Executive Committee Meetings (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Facilities, 1961-1965 (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Churchrock Feasibility Stude (Box 209, Folder 5)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Financing (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Long-Range Planning (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Maritime Nuclear Propulsion (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Prospectus, 1961-1963 (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Proposed Mergers and Acquisitions (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Proposed Mergers and Acquisitions - Cities Service Co. (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Proposed Mergers and Acquisitions -Douglas-United Nuclear (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Proposed Mergers and Acquisitions - NDA-Europe, S.A. (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Proposed Mergers and Acquisitions -Pan American Sulphur Co. (Box 210, Folder 7)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Quinta Corp. (Box 210, Folder 8)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Reorganization Plan (Drafts) (Box 210, Folder 9)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Sabre-Pinion Corp., 1962 (Box 211, Folder 1-4, Box 212, Folder 1)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Sanvik Special Metals Corp. (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Stockholders Meetings, 1961-1969 (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - United Nuclear Corporation - Stock Options, 1961-1967 (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - United Performing Arts, 1959-1961 (Box 212, Folder 5)
    Proposal for a united audience service/national organization to provide professional organizers and campaign directors to aid local civic music associations. TFW, HW, RHJ.
  - United States Borax and Chemical Corp. - General, 1955-1969 (Box 213, Folder 1)
    Produce potash, borates and laundry additives. Investment made. TFW, POC, CHB, D.W.
  - United States Borax and Chemical Corp. - Annuals, Stockholders, By-Laws (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - United States Borax and Chemical Corp. - Board of Directors, 1960-1969 (Box 213, Folder 3-5, Box 214, Folder 1-3, Box 215, Folder 1)
  - United States Borax and Chemical Corp. - Borax Holdings, Ltd. (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - United States Borax and Chemical Corp. - Discussions and Reports, 1965 (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - United States Borax and Chemical Corp. - Review of Research and Development Activities (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - United States Borax and Chemical Corp. - Summary, 1969 (Box 215, Folder 4)
  - United States Military Assistance Program, 1958-1959 (Box 215, Folder 5)
    Committee formed to study program. Preliminary conclusions. John McCloy of CMB participated. TFW, LSR.
  - Universal Business Machines - General, 1949-1954 (Box 215, Folder 6-8)
    Manufacture of office equipment. Investment made. WR, WJM, CES, L. Paige.
  - Universal Business Machines - Certificate of Incorporation, 1946 (Box 215, Folder 9)
  - Universal Business Machines - Ditto Contract, 1950-1959 (Box 216, Folder 1-2)
  - Universal Business Machines - Option Warrants, 1955-1963 (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - Universal Business Machines - Summary, undated (Box 216, Folder 4)
  - Universal Business Machines - Books of Account, 1946-1950 (Box 216, Folder 5, Box 217, Folder 1)
  - USICAF, 1962-1967 (Box 217, Folder 2-3)
    Usines Cotonnieres Africaines. Investment made. LSR, HW.
  - University of Vermont, 1949-1957 (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - VALCA, 1955-1956 (Box 218, Folder 2)
    Puerto Rican firm engaged in several businesses, including sugar, pineapples, bus Lines. Holds stock in Piasecki Helicopter Corp. CES, RHM, TFW, LSR, DR, WR.
  - Vertol-Boeing - General Correspondence, 1950-1960 (Box 218, Folder 3-4)
    Aircraft. Investment made.
  - Vertol-Boeing - Articles of Incorporation-By-Laws (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Board of Directors - Correspondence, 1954-1960 (Box 218, Folder 6, Box 219, Folder 1-2)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Board of Directors - Meetings, 1948-1959 (Box 219, Folder 3-6, Box 220, Folder 1-3)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Executive Committee Meetings, 1950-1959 (Box 220, Folder 4-6, Box 221, Folder 1-2)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Facilities, 1950-1959 (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Financial - Reviews, 1950-1959 (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Financial - V Loan, 1949-1956 (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Financial - New Financing, 1950-1951 (Box 221, Folder 5)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Foreign Activities - Europe - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 221, Folder 6)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Foreign Activities - Europe - Reviews, 1951-1953 (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Foreign Activities - Europe - Special Material, P. Bauer, 1959 (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Foreign Activities - Sales - PHC of Canada, 1951-1959 (Box 222, Folder 4)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Foreign Activities - Sales - Vertol 107 Model IV for Royal Canadian Navy, 1959 September (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Foreign Activities - Sales - PHC International, 1950-1959 (Box 223, Folder 1-2)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Inter-Office Memos, 1956-1959 (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Long Range Planning and Operations Research, 1957-1959 (Box 223, Folder 4)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Mergers - General, 1951-1960 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Mergers - Allied Research Associates, 1957-1958 (Box 224, Folder 1)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Mergers - Aeronca, 1956 (Box 224, Folder 2-3)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Mergers - Beech, 1957 (Box 224, Folder 4)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Mergers - Bell, 1958-1959 (Box 224, Folder 5-7, Box 225, Folder 1)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Mergers - Boeing, 1959-1960 (Box 225, Folder 2-3)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Mergers - Cessna, 1956 (Box 225, Folder 4)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Mergers - Hiller, 1959 (Box 225, Folder 5)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Mergers - Kaman, 1957 (Box 225, Folder 6)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Mergers - McDonnell, 1956-1958 (Box 225, Folder 7)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Mergers - Northrop, 1956-1957 (Box 225, Folder 8, Box 226, Folder 1-2)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Mergers - Northrop - Public Relations, 1956-1957 (Box 226, Folder 3)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Mergers - Northrop - Rockefeller and Voting Trust Agreement, 1957 (Box 227, Folder 1-2)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Mergers - Republic, 1957 (Box 227, Folder 3)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Mergers - Tool Research, 1959 (Box 227, Folder 4)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Mergers - Umbaugh, 1959 (Box 227, Folder 5)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Mergers - Vanguard Air and Marine, 1959 (Box 227, Folder 6)
  - Vertol-Boeing - New York Airways, 1959 (Box 227, Folder 7)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Competitor Studies, 1957-1959 (Box 227, Folder 8)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Public Relations - General, 1954-1959 (Box 228, Folder 1-5)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Public Relations - Program Recommendations, 1955 (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Public Relations - "Tandemeer", 1958-1959 (Box 229, Folder 2)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Research and Development, 1950-1959 (Box 229, Folder 3)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Reviews of Helicopter Industry, 1952-1958 (Box 229, Folder 4)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Brief History of the H-16 Program, 1956 (Box 230, Folder 1)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Stockholders Lists, 1950-1959 (Box 229, Folder 5)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Summary, 1949-1957 (Box 229, Folder 6)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Miscellaneous Stockholders Correspondence, 1948-1959 (Box 230, Folder 2)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Directors Compensation and Stock Option Committee, 1955-1959 (Box 231, Folder 1-3)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Stock Option Plan, 1953-1958 (Box 231, Folder 4)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Contracts - Status and Backlog, 1956-1960 (Box 231, Folder 5)
  - Piasecki - Subcontracts, 1951-1956 (Box 231, Folder 6)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Helicopter Status Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - Piasecki - Contract Status Reports - Overruns, 1953-1954 (Box 232, Folder 2)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Product Reviews, 1952-1954 (Box 232, Folder 3)
  - Vertol-Boeing - Work Sheets, 1949-1957 (Box 232, Folder 4)
  - Von Karman, Theodore, 1954-1963 (Box 233, Folder 1)
    Director of Institute for Advanced Aeronautical Study & Basic Research. Honors awarded him. TFW.
  - Wallace Aviation, 1954-1956 (Box 233, Folder 2-3)
    Manufacture aircraft parts. LSR investment HW, CHB, LSR.
  - Wayne-George Corp., 1961 (Box 233, Folder 4)
    Design, development, manufacture of digital transducers Stock purchase for 30 Rockefeller Plaza Associates & Co. TFW, HW, CHB.
  - Webb and Knapp, Inc., 1948-1966 (Box 233, Folder 5)
    Real estate company. Investment made by NAR and IBEC in Carbonic Products Corp. CHB, RHM.
  - Western Natural Gas Co., 1942-1962 (Box 233, Folder 6)
    Drilling operations along West Coast. Investment made in 1959. L. Paige, G. Moulton, JRD.
  - Western Hydrocarbon Co., 1956 (Box 233, Folder 7)
    Oil drilling. Stock held by NAR. RHM.
  - Wheeler Airlines - Air Transport Board License, 1959 (Box 233, Folder 8)
  - Wheeler Airlines - General, 1958-1960 (Box 234, Folder 1-3)
  - Wheeler Airlines - Equipment, 1956-1958 (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Wheeler Airlines - LSR Interest, 1958-1961 (Box 235, Folder 2)
  - Wheeler Airlines - R.H. Strange, 1961 (Box 235, Folder 3)
  - White Face Mountain Ski Area, 1963 (Box 235, Folder 4)
    Development of area, proposed resort. POC did study for the state conservation department. RWP, RMJ, POC.
  - Wiggins Airways, Inc., 1947-1963 (Box 235, Folder 5, Box 236, Folder 1)
    HW.
  - Western Europe - ELRON Electronics Industry - General, 1961-1967 (Box 236, Folder 2)
    JRD, RBM, HW, RHS, LSR, DR, CBS, TFW.
  - Western Europe - ELRON Electronics Industry - Directors Meetings, 1962-1965 (Box 236, Folder 3)
  - Western Europe - ELRON Electronics Industry - Michael Doren, 1961-1966 (Box 236, Folder 4)
  - Western Europe - ELRON Electronics Industry - Financing, 1962-1968 (Box 236, Folder 5-7, Box 237, Folder 1-3)
  - Western Europe - ELRON Electronics Industry - Stock Options, 1962-1968 (Box 237, Folder 4)
  - Western Europe - ELRON Electronics Industry - Stockholders Meetings, 1962-1965 (Box 237, Folder 5)
  - Western Europe - ELRON Electronics Industry - Summary, 1964-1965 (Box 237, Folder 6)
  - Western Europe - Icom - Annual Report - Operations, 1963-1964 (Box 237, Folder 7)
  - Western Europe - Icom ARCO - General, 1962-1964 (Box 238, Folder 1)
    Includes Directors Meetings and Falcheri Condenser.
  - Western Europe - Icom ARCO - A.D. Little Report, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 2)
  - Western Europe - Icom ARCO - C.B. Smith, 1961-1963 (Box 238, Folder 3, Box 239, Folder 1-2)
  - Western Europe - Icom ARCO - Financial Analyses, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - Western Europe - Icom ARCO - Summary, 1961-1964 (Box 239, Folder 4)
  - Western Europe - Icom ARCO - Financing, 1960-1964 (Box 240, Folder 1-3)
  - Western Europe - Icom ARCO - Financing - Sale to Olivetti, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - Western Europe - Icom ARCO - Financing - Allocation, 1963-1964 (Box 241, Folder 2)
  - Western Europe - ARS - General, 1961-1967 (Box 241, Folder 3-4)
  - Western Europe - ARS - Loan Guarantee, 1964 (Box 241, Folder 5)
  - Western Europe - ARS - Agreements (Box 241, Folder 6)
  - Western Europe - ARS - Agreements - Sale of Rockefeller Interest, 1964-1967 (Box 242, Folder 1)
  - Western Europe - ARS - Financing, 1961-1967 (Box 242, Folder 2-3, Box 243, Folder 1)
  - Western Europe - ARS - MHD Research, 1962-1963 (Box 242, Folder 4)
  - Western Europe - ARS - Raytheon Company, 1964 (Box 242, Folder 5)
  - Western Europe - ARS - SEMA, 1965 (Box 243, Folder 2)
  - Western Europe - ARS - Financing - Data - Stock Certificates, 1962-1965 (Box 243, Folder 3)
  - Western Europe - ARS - Stockholders Meetings, 1964-1967 (Box 243, Folder 4)
  - Western Europe - ARS - Summary, 1967 (Box 244, Folder 1)
  - Western Europe - HVL, SA - General, 1962-1967 (Box 244, Folder 2-3)
    Includes LSR-HVL agreement.
  - Western Europe - HVL, SA - Waterlet Report, 1965 (Box 244, Folder 4)
  - Western Europe - HVL, SA - Working Summary (Box 244, Folder 5)
  - Western Europe - Icom - Bolkow, 1960-1963 (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - Western Europe - Icom - Cominc, 1961-1962 (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - Western Europe - Icom - Derveaux, 1961 (Box 245, Folder 3)
  - Western Europe - Icom - Buachet and Cie, 1961 (Box 245, Folder 4)
  - Western Europe - Icom - Photo Produits Gevaert, 1961-1964 (Box 245, Folder 5)
  - Western Europe - Icom - Simonetta, 1961 (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - Western Europe - Icom - STV Rotary Pumps, 1961-1962 (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - Western Europe - Icom - Uher-Werke K.G., 1961-1962 (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Western Europe - Icom - V.E. Rimbotti, 1963-1965 (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Western Europe - Icom - Financial Correspondence, 1962-1966 (Box 246, Folder 5)
  - Western Europe - Icom - General - Brussels Office, 1959-1964 (Box 246, Folder 6-7, Box 247, Folder 1-3, Box 248, Folder 1-2)
  - Western Europe - Israel - General, 1961-1966 (Box 248, Folder 3)
    Includes Chase International Investment Corp.
  - Western Europe - Israel - American-Israel Chamber of Commerce, 1964-1965 (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - Western Europe - Israel - Israel Discount Bank, Ltd., 1968 (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - Western Europe - Israel - Technion, 1961-1966 (Box 249, Folder 3)
  - Western Europe - Israel - Yeda Research and Development, 1961 (Box 249, Folder 4)
  - Western Europe - Israel - Zion Chemical Products, 1961-1962 (Box 249, Folder 5)
- Investments, A-Z, Accession 2, 1949-1976; 2; 22.77 Cubic Feet 55 letter document boxes and 4 legal document boxes; Standard storage boxes, Boxes 115-135.
  - Africa-Tanganyika Concessions, 1949-1962 (Box 269, Folder 2)
  - Alaska Airlines Inc., 1961-1971 (Box 269, Folder 3)
  - Alyeska Ski Corp., 1967-1971 (Box 269, Folder 4)
  - Bara - Summary, 1967 (Box 270, Folder 1)
  - Bara - Liquidation File, 1967-1969 (Box 269, Folder 5)
  - Bara - Audits, 1963-1967 (Box 270, Folder 2)
  - Bara - By-Laws, 1964 (Box 270, Folder 3)
  - Bara - Contracts and Proposals, Research and Development, 1961-1969 (Box 270, Folder 4)
  - Bara - Directors Meetings, 1961-1968 (Box 270, Folder 5)
  - Bara - Financing, 1961-1967 (Box 271, Folder 1-4)
  - Bara - Financing - Dow Corning, 1963-1967 (Box 272, Folder 1)
  - Bara - Financing - Guaranty, 1961-1964 (Box 272, Folder 2)
  - Bara - C.B. Smith Office, 1961-1963 (Box 298, Folder 5)
  - Bara - General, 1961-1967 (Box 299, Folder 1-2)
  - Bara - Stockholders, 1964-1968 (Box 299, Folder 3)
  - Bara - Stock Option Pool, 1961-1964 (Box 299, Folder 4)
  - Barish - Royalty Payment, 1959-1968 (Box 299, Folder 5)
  - Barish - Summary, 1958-1964 (Box 300, Folder 1)
  - Barish - Offer to Purchase LSR Interest, 1961-1969 (Box 300, Folder 2)
  - Barish - Pioneer Aerodynamic Systems (Vortex Ring License Agreement), 1958 (Box 300, Folder 3)
  - Bauxi Congo (Seciete de Recherches et d'Exploitation des Bauxites), 1953-1972 (Box 301, Folder 1)
  - Belgian Congo - Investments, 1960-1970 (Box 301, Folder 2)
  - W.A. Benjamin Inc., 1961-1965 (Box 301, Folder 3)
  - CCI Corp. - Board of Directors, 1968-1971 (Box 272, Folder 3-5, Box 273, Folder 1)
  - Carbon Limestone Co., 1961-1968 (Box 273, Folder 2)
  - Caribbean Atlantic Airlines Inc. - Caribair Stock LSR, 1952-1969 (Box 273, Folder 3)
  - Commonwealth and European Trust (COMMET) - Selected Risk Mergers, 1961-1967 (Box 273, Folder 4)
  - Cerro Corp. - Board of Directors Meetings, 1969 (Box 274, Folder 1)
  - Cinema International - General, 1961-1967 (Box 274, Folder 2-3)
  - Cinema International - Correspondence, 1960-1972 (Box 275, Folder 1)
  - Cinema International - Accounting Reports and Financial Statements, 1964-1969 (Box 275, Folder 2)
  - Cinema International - Directors Meetings, 1961-1969 (Box 275, Folder 3, Box 276, Folder 1)
  - Cinema International - Westminster Theatres Files, 1961-1969 (Box 276, Folder 2-4)
  - Cinema International - Public Offerings, 1968 (Box 277, Folder 1)
  - Cinema International - Wardman Realty - Closing, 1960-1965 (Box 277, Folder 2)
  - Compat Corporation - Agreement - First National City Bank, 1971 (Box 276, Folder 5)
  - Compat Corporation - Agreement, Merger, 1970-1971 (Box 277, Folder 3)
  - Compat Corporation - Articles of Incorporation, By-Laws, 1970 (Box 276, Folder 6)
  - Compat Corporation - Board of Directors - Meetings - Agendas, 1969-1971 (Box 276, Folder 7)
  - Compat Corporation - Board of Directors - Meetings - Minutes, 1968-1971 (Box 278, Folder 1-3)
  - Compat Corporation - Executive Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 278, Folder 4)
  - Compat Corporation - Financial - Audit Reports, 1968-1970 (Box 278, Folder 5)
  - Compat Corporation - Financial - Correspondence and Reviews, 1968-1971 (Box 278, Folder 6)
  - Compat Corporation - Investment Memos, 1971 (Box 278, Folder 7)
  - Compat Corporation - Financing, 1968-1976 (Box 279, Folder 1-5)
  - Compat Corporation - Financing - Closing, 1976 (Box 277, Folder 4)
  - Compat Corporation - Investment Agreements, 1968-1970 (Box 279, Folder 6)
  - Compat Corporation - General, 1968-1971 (Box 279, Folder 7)
  - Compat Corporation - Merger Explorations, 1971 (Box 279, Folder 8)
  - Compat Corporation - Stock Options - Plans, 1968-1976 (Box 280, Folder 1)
  - Compat Corporation - Shevlin Stock, 1968-1970 (Box 280, Folder 2)
  - Compat Corporation - Stockholders - Meetings, 1968-1970 (Box 280, Folder 3)
  - Compat Corporation - Shareholders (Box 280, Folder 4)
  - Computone Systems Inc. - Agendas, 1969-1970 (Box 280, Folder 5)
  - Computone Systems Inc. - Minutes, 1962-1969 (Box 280, Folder 6)
  - Cutler Hammer Inc. - Airborne Inst. Labs., 1961-1973 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Deltec Investment Development - Deltec International, 1962-1968 (Box 281, Folder 2)
  - Eastern Airlines - Board of Directors and Finance Committee Meetings, 1969 (Box 281, Folder 3-4, Box 282, Folder 1-3, Box 283, Folder 1-4, Box 284, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Airlines - Board of Directors and Finance Committee Meetings, 1970 (Box 284, Folder 2-4, Box 285, Folder 1-4, Box 286, Folder 1-3)
  - Eastern Airlines - Board of Directors and Finance Committee Meetings, 1971 (Box 286, Folder 4, Box 287, Folder 1-4, Box 288, Box 289, Folder 1-3)
  - Eastern Airlines - Board of Directors and Finance Committee Meetings, 1972 (Box 289, Folder 4, Box 290, Folder 1-4, Box 291, Box 292, Folder 1-2)
  - Execuplane, 1959-1968 (Box 301, Folder 4)
  - Explorer Fund, 1969 (Box 302, Folder 1)
  - Fazenda Bodoquend, S.A., 1957-1968 (Box 302, Folder 2)
  - Family Aircraft, 1964-1970 (Box 302, Folder 3)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - Annual Reports, 1966-1972 (Box 302, Folder 4)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - Browne and Shaw Study, 1968 (Box 302, Folder 5)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - Fund Raising, 1961-1965 (Box 302, Folder 6)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - Fund Raising Organizations, 1959-1962 (Box 303, Folder 1)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - General, 1964-1967 (Box 303, Folder 2)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - Meetings, 1962-1970 (Box 303, Folder 3-4)
  - Foran Foundry and Manufacturing, 1958-1968 (Box 303, Folder 5)
  - Geophysics Corporation of America (GCA) - Board of Directors Meetings, 1969 January-1970 December (Box 304, Folder 1-4)
  - Geophysics Corporation of America (GCA) - Board of Directors Meetings, 1971 January-1972 December (Box 305, Folder 1-3)
  - Geophysics Corporation of America (GCA) - Mergers - Alpha Metals Inc., 1967-1969 (Box 305, Folder 4)
  - Geophysics Corporation of America (GCA) - Mergers - Vacuum Specialties, 1961 (Box 305, Folder 5)
  - Geophysics Corporation of America (GCA) - Mergers - Itek Agreement, 1958-1968 (Box 306, Folder 1)
  - Geophysics Corporation of America (GCA) - Mergers - Ranco, 1968-1970 (Box 306, Folder 2)
  - GTI Corporation, 1961-1964 (Box 306, Folder 3)
    Biographical / Historical
    Formerly Glass-Tite
  - Garden State Paper Company, Inc., 1960-1966 (Box 306, Folder 4)
  - General Technologies Corp. - Board of Directors Meetings, 1962-1968 (Box 307, Folder 1)
  - General Technologies Corp. - Financial Audit, 1968 (Box 307, Folder 2)
  - General Technologies Corp. - Financing, 1964-1965 (Box 307, Folder 3-5)
    Including but not limited to Thermo Kinetic Fibers.
  - General Technologies Corp. - By-Laws, Patents (Box 308, Folder 1)
  - General Technologies Corp. - General, 1962-1971 (Box 308, Folder 2-3)
  - General Technologies Corp. - Lexington Labs - Johns Manville, 1963-1965 (Box 308, Folder 4)
  - General Technology Corp. - Nutley Liquidating Corp., 1963-1968 (Box 308, Folder 5)
  - General Technologies Corp. - Stockholders Lists, 1965-1966 (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - General Technologies Corp. - Stockholder Meetings, 1963-1969 (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - General Technologies Corp. - Thermo Kinetic Fibers - Stock Option (Box 309, Folder 3)
  - General Technologies Corp. - Summary, 1960s (Box 309, Folder 4)
  - General Technology Corp. - Tracor Inc. - Distribution of Stock - ARM, DR, LSR, 1965-1967 (Box 309, Folder 5)
  - General Technology Corp. - Financing, 1964 (Box 310, Folder 1-2)
  - General Technology Corp. - Tracor Plan and Agreement Reorganization, 1965 (Box 310, Folder 3)
  - Groupement Immobilier European D'Etudes et de Participations (GIEP), 1969-1971 (Box 310, Folder 4)
  - Honolulu Production Payments, 1963-1972 (Box 310, Folder 5, Box 311, Folder 1-3)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - General, 1959-1961 (Box 312, Folder 1)
  - Itek - Board of Directors Meetings, 1968-1971 (Box 312, Folder 2-5)
  - Itek - General, 1960-1967 (Box 313, Folder 1)
  - Itek - Mergers - Alfa Gevaert, 1968 (Box 313, Folder 2)
  - Itek - Mergers - Chicago Aerial Ind., 1971 (Box 313, Folder 3)
  - Itek - Mergers - Dohan Labs Inc., 1969 (Box 313, Folder 4)
  - Itek - Mergers - Eastman Kodak, 1965 (Box 313, Folder 5)
  - Itek - Mergers - Foreign Market ETI, 1968 (Box 313, Folder 6)
  - Itek - Mergers - GCA Dispute, 1968 (Box 314, Folder 1)
  - Itek - Mergers - Readex-Microprint Corp., 1968 (Box 314, Folder 2)
  - Itek - Mergers - Time, Inc. - Agreement - Financing, 1968 (Box 314, Folder 3)
  - Itek - Mergers - Vidya, 1959 -1965 (Box 314, Folder 4)